Guide to the Brian R. McNaught papers, circa 1970-2004
McNaught, Brian R. papers, circa 1970-2004
- Series IV. Catholic and Unitarian Universalist
  - Dignity - an organization for gay Catholics
    - Dignity - Boston, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Dignity - Boston, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Dignity - Boston - Newsletter, 1976-1983 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Dignity - Chicago, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Dignity Columns (copies), n.d. (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Dignity Convention, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Dignity - Detroit, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
    - Dignity - Detroit, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dignity - Detroit, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dignity Handbook, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Dignity - National, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dignity - National, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Dignity - State Chapters, 1976-1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Dignity - Tampa Bay, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Dignity Detroit 25th/27th Anniversary Materials, 1999,2001 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Dignity Detroit History, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Episcopal Urban Caucus, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gay/ Catholic issues - includes Salvatorian Gay Ministry, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - In Unity magazine, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Insight magazine, 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 14-16)
  - Insight magazine, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Michigan Catholic demonstration - articles, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Michigan Catholic: Legal Documents on Case, 1974 (Box 5, Folder Oversize)
  - Michigan Catholic Readership Survey, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Michigan Catholic Readership Survey, 1973 (Box 6, Folder Oversize)
  - National Center for Gay Ministry, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - National Task Force of Gay People in the Church, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Newsletters and other information - Christian, 1973-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Catholic magazine, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Young Adult Ministry, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Catholic/Gay material, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - New Ways Ministry 25th Anniversary Symposium, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Welcoming Congregation- Unitarian Universalist Church, Naples, FL, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Dignity Detroit (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - "Baptism and the Experience of 'Coming Out'." 6th National Symposium on Catholocism and Homosexuality [contains two audio CDs] (Box 23, Folder 79)
- Series V. Boston
  This series contains Brian McNaught's files from his time as the Liaison to the mayor for the gay and lesbian community, 1982-1984. Included in this series are testimony and materials from the "Boston Project," started by mayor Kevin H. White and designed to improve life in Boston for the gay and lesbian community. Also included are various files about Boston, such as police files, local events, and a file on the Beantown softball league.
  - The Boston Project - "toward an agenda for gay and lesbian citizens"- transcripts, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 26-28)
  - Boston Project - Miscellaneous information, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Boston Project - Letter to Gay and Lesbian Community from Brian McNaught, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Files from when Brian McNaught served as the Liaison to the Gay and Lesbian Community in Boston for Mayor Kevin H. White, 1982-1984
    - Arts, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Beantown Softball League, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Boston Intercollegiate Gay and Lesbian Alliance (BIGLA), 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Billing, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Boston Lesbian and Gay Political Alliance (BLGPA), 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
    - Boards, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Briefings, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Bulletin Board, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Community Center, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Complaints, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Cable Television, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Constituent Mail Report, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Daily Log, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
    - The Deep Backgrounder, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Department Heads, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Discrimination, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Education - Departments, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Fire, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - GALPONE, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Gay Groups, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Gay Olympics, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Gay Olympic Games, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Gay Task Force, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - GCN - Gay Community News, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - GLAD - Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Glad Day Bookstore, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Goals for Boston, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Homeless, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Hub Association, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Lesbian and Gay Projects, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Liaison, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 33-34)
    - Liaison Hiring, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
    - Liaison - Letters, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Library, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Licensing, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Memorandum, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Mitzel, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Mapplethorp, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Nambla, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Not Hired for Liaison Position, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 44-45)
    - Pamphlets - Miscellaneous, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Partners, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Permits, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Pine Street, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Police, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 50-52)
    - Police Cadets, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Police Liaison, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Press, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Prison, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Resumes, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Student Intern, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Unitarians, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Veterans Services, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Watchline Project, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Series VI. Subject Files
  This series contains Brian McNaught's files relevant to his work. Included in this series are his files on AIDS information, files on specific people and gay and/or Catholic organizations such as the National Gay Task Force, the Thornfield workshop, and two Marches on Washington. There is information on a variety of gay and lesbian issues in the form of reports and articles.
  - AIDS
    - AIDS Action Committee - Buddies, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - AIDS Articles, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - AIDS Brochures, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
    - Cape Ann AIDS Education, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
    - Cape Ann AIDS Leadership Forum, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Cape Ann AIDS Support, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - AIDS - Gloucester, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - AIDS Information (Early), 1980s (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
    - AIDS Information, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - AIDS - Manager's Kit - Responding to AIDS: Workplace Policy, Employee Education, Resources, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17-19)
    - AIDS Patients - Adam and Phil (and more), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - AIDS Workshop Information, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Akron Speaking Engagement, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - American Society for Sex Educators, Counselors and Therapists (AASECT), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - AASECT Conference - San Francisco, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - AASECT - Gay Male/ Lesbian Couples, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Appeals, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - "As Is" (Play), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Atlanta Politics, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Background Information for Column, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Baker, Jack, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Barbo, Beverly, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Body Electric, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Boston Project Survey, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Brill, David, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Bush Report, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Campus Project, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Carter, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Catholic Advocates for Equality, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Catholic Conference, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 39-40)
  - Charlene and Rick, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Party, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Party, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Gay Clergy - Milwaukee Sentinel, Jun. 1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Personal Privacy, Nov. 1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Congregation of Christian Brothers, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Data, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cruising, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Custody, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dan, 1974-1994 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Definition News Agency, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Denver, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Dowling, James (AIDS Patient), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Dowling's Pornography Collection, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - Drinan, Robert, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Eastern College Students' Reaction Papers to a McNaught Speech, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Ecker, Thomas, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Ed-U Press, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Elmira College, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Empathy, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Endean, Steve, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Exodus Center, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Exodus Center, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Exodus from the Closet by Patrick Scanlon (manuscript), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 26-27)
  - Fairness Fund, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Family Protection Act, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Fast: Articles and Letters about, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Fenway Community Health Center, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Fiction/ Poems not by McNaught, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Fiero, Pat - money, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Front Runner - Movie, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Films, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 35-36)
  - Fund for Fairness and Privacy, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Future Stuff, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Gainesville, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Gay Chicago, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Gay Christian, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Gay Community News, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Gay Democrats, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Gay Games, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Gay and Lesbian Counseling Service (GLCS), 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 46-47)
  - Gay Pride, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Gays - Reports and Political Articles, 1975-1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Gay Rights National Lobby (GRNL), 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Gay Speaker's Bureau, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Gay Writer's Conference - Allen Young, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Ginder, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Sol Gordon, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "Grogg the Frog" poem by McNaught, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Guidance Associates, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "Homosexuality - the Moral Issue" no author, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Homosexual Rights Bill - clippings and information, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Hospitals and Health, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund (HCRF) - San Antonio, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Human Rights Press, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Identity - Alaska, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Integrity, 1975-1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Jackson, Jim, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Jamie (no last name mentioned), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Justice for Gay People, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Khurana, Nimmi - Ontario, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Kosnik, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Laos, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Laws, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Lawrence University, Jan. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Lazarus Project, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Legislation re: Homosexuals, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Legislation - State, 1983-1989 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Literature and Pamphlets, 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 28-30)
  - Lively Word, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - March on Washington D.C., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - March on Washington D.C., 1993 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Mariposa, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Marquette Alums, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Married Gays, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Massachusetts Business Association, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Massachusetts Gay and Lesbian Political Caucus (MGPC), 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Masturbation, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - METRA- Michigan, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Michigan Catholic - Articles and more on Hunger Strike, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 41-44)
  - Michigan Catholic - Diary and Papers, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 45-47)
  - Monitor Article, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Moral Majority, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - National Association for Campus Activities (NACA), 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - National Federation of Priests' Councils (NFPC), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF), 1975-1989 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - National Gay Task Force - Male Resource, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Network Q, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - New Ways Ministry, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - New York Gay Rights Bill, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Northland Companion, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Nurses - Attitudes Toward Male Homosexuals, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - On Being Gay - book and video
    - Advertisements for video, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Book - Miscellaneous (and some Disturbed Peace), 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 15-16)
    - Book Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Video Promotional Copies, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Video Promotional Miscellaneous (includes photos), 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Video Reviews, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Video Promotion, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 21-22)
    - Promotional Pamphlets, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - O'Neill, Pat - United States Catholic Conference - Pastoral Statement, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Ordinances, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Out, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Outing Magazine, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Personal Material of McNaught, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Playbills, 1975-1985 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Positively Gay, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Positively Gay - Gay in the Workplace, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - PRAD, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Presbyterians, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Presidential Inauguration Invitation, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Press Releases/Informational Letters, 1976-1986 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Prime Timers, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Proctor Academy, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Problem/Need Gay Community, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Resource/Speech Materials, 1980-1989 (Box 11, Folder 38-45)
  - Roberts, Bill, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Rofes - Handbook, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Sad Dilemma of the Gay Catholic, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Safe Sex, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - SAG - Study/Action Guide vol. II - Which Side are You on?, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - S.A.G.E., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - S.A.G.E. Working Committee, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "The Saint at Large" posters, 1986-1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Sanger Award - "for distinguished service in the field of Responsible Sex", 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Sentinel USA, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Sex Education - pamphlets, papers and letters, 1976-1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Shanley, Rev. Paul, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Silvestre, Anthony, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sipple, Oliver, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Social Action Chair Persons, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Speech Duplicates, 1973-1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Spiritual Journey, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - STUDDS Fundraising Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Syracuse University Sex Education Materials, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Tatum, Mary Lee, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Thornfield - Sexuality Workshop/Retreat, 1985-1993 (Box 12, Folder 21-29)
  - US Catholic, 1975-1987 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Video/Newsletter Promotional Pamphlets and Other Material, 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Witness, Jun. 1979 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Young Adult Ministry, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Youngstown, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Youth, 1984-1988 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Human Rights Campaign, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Hate mail to Rep. Gerry Studds, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Liz Winfield and Sue Spielman, book on Gays in the Workplace information, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Confidential plan on gay marriage in Florida of group Red and Blue (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Confidential battle plan on Equality Florida in winning civil rights for gay and transgender people (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Communication from LOGO on gay programming (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Gay-related newsletters and workplace guides from Stonewall in London (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Lehman Brothers employee network booklets (Box 23, Folder 83)
- Series VII. Correspondence
  This series consists of personal letters and other correspondence received by Brian McNaught from 1965-1998. There are letters from bishops and priests, heads of Dignity chapters, and personal letters from friends, as well as business correspondence. Of note are statements of support from numerous people during his hunger strike, including the letter ending his 1974 fast. Also included in this series is fan mail about his various books as well as letters from friends and family. Some letters have been RESTRICTED UNTIL 2049 or 2033 by the donor.
  - A Disturbed Peace Letters, 1981-1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence and Letters
    - General Correspondence and Letters, 1970-1979 (Box 13, Folder 2-7)
    - General Correspondence and Letters, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence and Letters, 1980-1989 (Box 13, Folder 9-14)
    - General Correspondence and Letters, 1990-1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence and Letters, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Michigan Catholic Hunger Strike - Letters, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 17-19)
  - Michigan Catholic Hunger Strike - Statements of Support, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - On Being Gay - Letters about book, 1987-1992 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - "On Being Gay" - Letters about video, 1986-1991 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Contact Mail [ RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - A Disturbed Peace (book) - Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Family Letters
    - Family Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1973-1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Family Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1980-1998 (Box 14, Folder 4-8)
    - Family Letters about his Father [ RESTRICTED], 1965-1995 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Fan Mail/General Correspondence
    - Fan Mail/General Correspondence [ RESTRICTED], 1965-1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Fan Mail/General and Personal Correspondence [ RESTRICTED], 1970-1979 (Box 14, Folder 11-20)
    - Fan Mail/General Correspondence [ RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Fan Mail/General Correspondence [ RESTRICTED], 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 22-27)
    - Fan Mail/General Correspondence [ RESTRICTED], 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
    - Fan Mail/General Correspondence [ RESTRICTED], 1990-1998 (Box 15, Folder 5-7)
    - Fan Mail/General Correspondence [ RESTRICTED], 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
  - Friends' Letters
    - Friends' Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1970-1979 (Box 15, Folder 10-13)
    - Friends' Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Friends' Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1970-1998 (Box 15, Folder 15-18)
    - Friends' Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 19-25)
    - Friends' Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 26-30)
    - Friends' Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1980-1989 (Box 16, Folder 1-16)
  - Grix, Henry (Best Friend and Attorney) [ RESTRICTED], 1970-1979 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - "Impact" Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 18-19)
  - Michigan Catholic/Hunger Strike - Letters of Support [ RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 20-25)
  - Name withheld [ RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - On Being Gay (book) - letters [ RESTRICTED], 1987-1992 (Box 16, Folder 27-32)
  - "On Being Gay" (video) - letters [ RESTRICTED], 1986-1989 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Responses to U.S. Catholic Article [ RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Struble, Ray - cards and letters to and from [ RESTRICTED], 1976-1998 (Box 16, Folder 35-36)
  - Misc. correspondence, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence from "notables" (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence with Sol Gordon, 2000-2003 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Personal e-mails (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - AASECT Nominating Committee Correspondence [ RESTRICTED], 1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Gay Salvation Army Letters [ RESTRICTED], 1998-2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Letters/e-mails [ RESTRICTED], 1998-2003 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Personal Letters/e-mails [ RESTRICTED], 1999-2002 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - "Personalities" Letters/e-mails [ RESTRICTED], 1999-2001 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Personal Letters/e-mails [ RESTRICTED], 2002 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Gay Salvation Army Letters [ RESTRICTED], 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - People seeking help (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - "Names You Might Know" (includes Bishop John Sprong, Carson Kressley, Gregory Maguire, Sol Gordon, Jeannine Gramick, Joan Garry, Kevin Jennings, and others) (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Proposed book on Manager's Guide to Gay and Transgender Issues (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Gay workplace mail [relating to work in corporations on gay and transgender issues] (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Rejection letters on Are You Guys Brothers? (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - College student responses to book Sex Camp. [required reading for 500 students at the University of Maine] (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence from readers of "Sex Camp" (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Gay and lesbian wedding announcements (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Paul Shanley [ RESTRICTED] (Box 24)
  - Salvation Army captain [ RESTRICTED] (Box 24)
- Series VIII. Support Documents
  Support Documents include articles about McNaught and reviews of his writing; also, magazines, brochures, and pamphlets McNaught saved that are relevant to his work. Some publications were separated to be cataloged as part of the Human Sexuality Collection print resources. See: Separated Materials.
  - Miscellaneous Articles
    - Miscellaneous Articles, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, 1975-1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, 1985-1995 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
  - Articles and Brochures
    - Articles and Brochures, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Articles and Brochures, 1970-1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Articles and Brochures, 1980-1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Brochures and Pamphlets
    - Brochures and Pamphlets, 1975-1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Brochures and Pamphlets, 1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Brochures and Pamphlets, 1974-1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Brochures and Pamphlets, 1982-1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Brochures and Pamphlets, 1985-1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Pamphlets, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Clippings and Articles
    - Clippings and Articles, 1969-1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Clippings and Articles, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - Clippings and Articles, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Clippings and Articles, 1976-1983 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Clippings and Articles about McNaught, 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Gay Rights/Religion Articles
    - Gay Rights/Religion Articles, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 19-21)
    - Gay Rights and other Articles, 1974-1985 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Pamphlets and Papers
    - Pamphlets and Papers, 1978-1982 (Box 17, Folder 23-24)
    - Pamphlets and Papers, 1994-1998 (Box 17, Folder 25-26)
  - Playbills dealing with Gay issues, 1985-1995 (Box 17, Folder 27-28)
  - Publications